Guide to the Robert Louis Laing McCormick Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Robert Louis Laing McCormick papers
1945-1971
MS 338
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
36.25
(40 boxes)
Correspondence, memoranda, press releases, printed matter, and reports pertaining to the Citizens Committee for the Hoover Report (1948-1958), postwar Germany, the 1968 election, the Veterans Administration, and environmental policies. The papers also contain correspondence, reports and printed matter of Charles E. Smith (1948-1957) and correspondence, memoranda, reports etc. on the American Tariff League, Inc. (1955-1959) and the Trade Relations Council of the United States (1959-1963).
McCormick, Robert Louis Laing, 1917-1975
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Robert L.L. McCormick, 1965, and Dorothy McCormick, 1983.
Arrangement
Arranged in four series and one addition: I. Citizens Committee for the Hoover Report. II. Trade Relations Council Files. III. Trade Files. IV. Publications.
Biographical / Historical
Government official; A.B., Yale 1940; held various positions with the government throughout WW II; assistant to the chairman of the 1st Hoover Commission, 1947-1949; director of research for the Citizens Committee for Hoover Report, 1949-1954, research consultant, 1954-1961; consultant 2nd Hoover Commission, 1953-1955; vice president of Coates & McCormick, Inc., 1952-1956; president of McCormick Associates, Inc., 1957-1965; director of research for Republican National Committee, 1965-1969.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence, memoranda, press releases, printed matter, and reports pertaining to the Citizens Committee for the Hoover Report (1948-1958), postwar Germany, the 1968 election, the Veterans Administration, and environmental policies. The papers also contain correspondence, reports and printed matter of Charles E. Smith (1948-1957) and correspondence, memoranda, reports etc. on the American Tariff League, Inc. (1955-1959) and the Trade Relations Council of the United States (1959-1963).
Professional associations -- United States; United States -- Foreign relations -- 1945-1953; United States -- Politics and government -- 1945-1953; Public officers; Trade associations -- United States; United States -- Foreign relations -- 1945-1989; United States -- Politics and government -- 1945-1989; McCormick, Robert Louis Laing, 1917-1975; Smith, Charles E.; United States. Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government (1947-1949); United States. Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government (1953-1955); American Tariff League; Citizens Committee for the Hoover Report; Trade Relations Council of the United States
- CITIZENS COMMITTEE FOR THE HOOVER REPORT (CCHR) FILES, Series I
  - Chronological Files
    - General, 1949 March - October 15 (Box 1, Folder 1-12)
    - General, 1949 October 16 - 1950 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 13-28)
    - General, 1950 May 16 - 1951 March 15 (Box 3, Folder 29-47)
    - General, 1951 March 16 - December 15 (Box 4, Folder 48-64)
    - General, 1951 December 16 - 1952 September 15 (Box 5, Folder 65-80)
    - General, 1952 September 16 - 1953 August 31 (Box 6, Folder 81-95)
    - General, 1953 November 1 - 1956 June 9 (Box 7, Folder 96-108)
    - General, 1956 June 10 - 1957 March 31 (Box 8, Folder 109-124)
    - General, 1957 April 1 - August 15 (Box 9, Folder 125-138)
    - General, 1957 August 16 - 1958 March 31 (Box 10, Folder 139-153)
    - General, 1958 April 1 - December (Box 11, Folder 154-164)
    - Information bulletins, 1955 May - 1956 May (Box 11, Folder 165-169)
    - Information bulletins, 1956 May - 1958 July 15 (Box 12, Folder 170-177)
    - Press clippings, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 178)
    - Press releases, 1949 March - 1950 January (Box 12, Folder 179-186)
    - Press releases, 1950 January - 1951 March (Box 13, Folder 187-200)
    - Press releases, 1951 March - 1952 May (Box 14, Folder 201-214)
    - Press releases, 1952 May - July (Box 15, Folder 215-217)
    - Special bulletins, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 218-219)
    - Special research memoranda, 1955-1957 (Box 15, Folder 220-223)
  - Subject Files
    - 81st and 82nd Congress
      - Action sheets (Box 15, Folder 224)
      - Circular letters (Box 15, Folder 225)
      - Chronological, 1950-1952 (Box 15, Folder 226-227)
      - Committee Reporter, undated (Box 15, Folder 228)
      - Discussion Guide Series, undated (Box 15, Folder 229)
      - General, undated (Box 15, Folder 230)
      - Government Operations Committees reports, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 231-232)
      - The Heart of the Hoover Report, undated (Box 16, Folder 233)
      - "Here's How...", undated (Box 16, Folder 234)
      - Publications, 1949-1952 (Box 16, Folder 235-239)
      - "Reorganization News", 1949-1952 (Box 16, Folder 240)
      - Reorganization Record, 1949-1952 (Box 16, Folder 241)
      - Savings, 1949-1952 (Box 16, Folder 242)
      - "Washington Watchdog", 1950-1952 (Box 16, Folder 243-246)
      - "What the Hoover...", undated (Box 17, Folder 247)
      - 1st National Reorganization Conference, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 248)
      - 2nd National Reorganization Conference, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 249-250)
    - 83rd Congress
      - Bibliography, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 251)
      - Brassor, Francis, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 252)
      - Establishment of 2nd Hoover Commission, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 253-254)
      - General, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 255-256)
      - Government Operations Committee Reports, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 257)
      - Hollister, John, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 258)
      - Independent Agencies report, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 259-261)
      - Independent Agencies report, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 262-266)
      - Press releases, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 267-268)
      - Public laws, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 269-271)
      - Publications, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 272-273)
      - Reorganization Act of 1949, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 274)
      - Task forces, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 275-277)
    - 84th Congress
      - Democratic convention, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 278)
      - Metz studies, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 279-280)
      - Publications, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 281-282)
      - "Under the Bridge" Project (Box 19, Folder 283-284)
    - 85th Congress
      - Brown, Congressman Clarence J., 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 285)
      - Clippings, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 286)
      - Coates, Charles B., 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 287)
      - Congressional reports, hearings, bill, 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 288)
      - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 289-291)
      - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 292-293)
      - Defense Department, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 294)
      - Files: Hoover Library, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 295)
      - Finances, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 296)
      - Francis, Clarence, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 297-298)
      - Furniture, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 299)
      - Hoover, Herbert, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 300)
      - Letters to organizations, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 301)
      - Memos, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 302)
      - Omnibus bill, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 303)
      - Publications, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 304-305)
      - Reorganization News, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 306)
    - 1958
      - Briefing session, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 307)
      - Climax Drive Workshop, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 308)
      - Confidential, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 309)
      - Diaries, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 310-313)
      - Government Operations Commission, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 314-315)
      - Kestnbaum, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 316-318)
      - Lists, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 319-321)
      - Lists, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 322-323)
      - Memoranda, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 324-325)
      - Office business, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 326)
      - Office equipment, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 327)
      - Personnel-staff, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 328)
      - Presidential messages, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 329-330)
      - Press releases, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 331-334)
      - Public laws, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 335)
      - Publications, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 336-345)
      - Savings, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 346-353)
      - Third National Reorganization Conference, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 354-355)
  - Commission on the organization of the Executive Branch of the Government, 1947-1949 (First Hoover Commission)
    - Reports
      - Outline, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 356)
      - Personnel (Box 25, Folder 357)
      - General Services (Box 25, Folder 358)
      - Post Office (Box 25, Folder 359)
      - Foreign Affairs (Box 25, Folder 360)
      - Agriculture (Box 25, Folder 361)
      - Budget and Accounting (Box 25, Folder 362)
      - National Security Organization (Box 25, Folder 363)
      - Veterans Administration (Box 25, Folder 364)
      - Commerce (Box 25, Folder 365)
      - Treasury (Box 25, Folder 366)
      - Regulatory Commissions (Box 25, Folder 367)
      - Labor (Box 25, Folder 368)
      - Interior (Box 25, Folder 369)
      - Indian Affairs (Box 26, Folder 370)
      - Medical Activities (Box 26, Folder 371)
      - Business Enterprises (Box 26, Folder 372)
      - Overseas Administration (Box 26, Folder 373)
      - Concluding Report (Box 26, Folder 374)
    - Task Force studies
      - General Management (Box 27, Folder 375-390)
      - Personnel Management (Box 28, Folder 391-401)
      - General Services (Box 28, Folder 402-407)
      - Foreign Affairs (Box 29, Folder 408-416)
      - Budgeting and Accounting (Box 29, Folder 417-428)
      - General Services (Box 30, Folder 429-431)
      - Foreign Affairs (Box 30, Folder 432-445)
      - Budgeting and Accounting (Box 31, Folder 446-451)
      - National Security Organization (Box 31, Folder 452-470)
      - Veterans Administration (Box 32, Folder 471-477)
      - Commerce (Box 32, Folder 478-493)
      - Commerce (Box 33, Folder 494-518)
      - Commerce (Box 34, Folder 519-538)
      - Commerce (Box 35, Folder 539-558)
      - Labor (Box 36, Folder 559-562)
      - Indian Affairs (Box 36, Folder 563-575)
      - Medical Activities (Box 36, Folder 576-582)
      - Medical Activities (Box 37, Folder 583-606)
      - Business Enterprises (Box 38, Folder 607-624)
  - Commission on the organization of the Executive Branch of the Government, 1953-1955 (Second Hoover Commission)
    - Reports
      - Budget and Accounting (Box 39, Folder 625)
      - Business Enterprises (Box 39, Folder 626)
      - Business Organization of the Dept. of Defense (Box 39, Folder 627)
      - Depot Utilization (Box 39, Folder 628)
      - Federal Medical Services (Box 39, Folder 629)
      - Food and Clothing (Box 39, Folder 630)
      - Intelligence Activities (Box 39, Folder 631)
      - Legal Services and Procedures (Box 39, Folder 632)
      - Lending Agencies (Box 39, Folder 633)
      - Overseas Economic Operations (Box 39, Folder 634)
      - Paperwork Management (Box 40, Folder 635-636)
      - Personnel and Civil Service (Box 40, Folder 637)
      - Real Property Management (Box 40, Folder 638)
      - Research and Development (Box 40, Folder 639)
      - Surplus Property (Box 40, Folder 640)
      - Transportation (Box 40, Folder 641)
      - Water Resources and Power (Box 40, Folder 642-643)
      - Progress Report (Box 41, Folder 644)
      - Final Report (Box 41, Folder 645)
      - Digest and Analysis Report (Box 41, Folder 646)
    - Staff papers
      - Comparative Print (Box 42, Folder 647-648)
      - Correspondence (Box 42, Folder 649)
      - Department of Defense: Business Organization (Box 42, Folder 650-654)
      - Department of Defense: Defense Procurement (Box 42, Folder 655-668)
      - Department of Defense: Defense Procurement (Box 43, Folder 669-677)
      - Federal Medical Services (Box 43, Folder 678-686)
      - Federal Medical Services (Box 44, Folder 687-695)
      - Legal Services and Procedure (Box 44, Folder 696-706)
      - Legal Services and Procedure (Box 45, Folder 707-710)
      - Paperwork Management (Box 45, Folder 711-712)
  - Photographs
    - CCHR Briefing Session, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 713)
    - Hoover Commissions, undated (Box 46, Folder 714-720)
    - Third National Reorganization Conference, undated (Box 46, Folder 721-726)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Charles Smith: correspondence and printed material, 1948-1949 (Box 46, Folder 727-730)
- TRADE RELATIONS COUNCIL FILES, Series II
  - American Tariff League
    - General correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 47, Folder 731-744)
    - Administrative memoranda, 1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 745)
    - Confidential reports, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 746)
    - Minutes: annual meetings, 1955-1958 (Box 48, Folder 747-762)
    - Research bulletins: vol. I (Box 48, Folder 763-767)
    - Research bulletins: vol. II (Box 49, Folder 768)
    - Topical files
      - Antidumping, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 769-770)
      - Authoritative study, 1956-1958, undated (Box 49, Folder 771-776)
      - Board of Managers, 1956-1959 (Box 49, Folder 777-779)
      - Chamber of Commerce, 1957-1959, undated (Box 49, Folder 780-782)
      - Customs simplification, 1956, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 783)
      - Dinners: fund raising, 1956, 1957, undated (Box 50, Folder 784-787)
      - Dinners: Sheraton-Carlton, 1957, 1958, undated (Box 50, Folder 788-789)
      - Employment statistics, 1958, undated (Box 50, Folder 790)
      - Fund raising letters, 1958, undated (Box 50, Folder 791)
      - G.A.T.T., 1955, 1956, undated (Box 50, Folder 792-793)
      - Import-affected industries, 1958, undated (Box 50, Folder 794)
      - Inter-office memoranda, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 795)
      - Ketchum, MacLeod and Grove, Inc., 1958 (Box 50, Folder 796)
      - Knox, Congressman: speech, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 797)
      - Luncheon meetings, 1958, undated (Box 50, Folder 798-802)
      - Nationwide Committee on Import-Export Policy, 1956-1958 (Box 51, Folder 803-806)
      - N.A.T.O., 1957 (Box 51, Folder 807)
      - Operation Build-Up, 1956, 1957, undated (Box 51, Folder 808)
      - Phillips "66", 1956 (Box 51, Folder 809)
      - Platform: Democratic National Convention, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 810)
      - Press releases, 1957-1959 (Box 51, Folder 811)
      - Publications, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 812)
      - Reed: speech, 1958, 1959, undated (Box 51, Folder 813)
      - Report to Congress, 1957, undated (Box 51, Folder 814)
      - Rockefeller report, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 815)
      - State studies, 1953-1956, undated (Box 51, Folder 816-821)
      - Stevens, Robert T., 1958, undated (Box 52, Folder 822)
      - Stewart, Eugene, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 823)
      - Stricker, Adam K., Jr., 1957, 1958, undated (Box 52, Folder 824-826)
      - Trade Information Committee, 1956-1959, undated (Box 52, Folder 827)
      - Trade Policy Committee, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 828)
    - Legislation
      - Antidumping Act, 1957, 1958, undated (Box 52, Folder 829-830)
      - Bills: House, 85th Congress, 1957, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 831-833)
      - Bills: Senate, 85th Congress, 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 834-835)
      - Boggs subcommittee, 1956-1959, undated (Box 53, Folder 836-839)
      - Bolling subcommittee hearings, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 840)
      - Butlard statement to House Ways and Means subcommittee, undated (Box 53, Folder 841)
      - Committee Reports: House and Senate, 85th Congress, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 842)
      - Congressional Hotel material, 1958, undated (Box 53, Folder 843-844)
      - Congressional Record: Floor Debate on H.R. 12591, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 845)
      - Congressional statements on Extension of Trade Agreements Act, 1958, undated (Box 53, Folder 846)
      - Congressional: miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 847)
      - Davis (Rep.): Reprint and press release on T.A.E.A., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 848)
      - Differences between Senate and House versions of H.R. 12591, undated (Box 53, Folder 849)
      - Dorn (Rep.): T.A.E.A., 1958., undated (Box 53, Folder 850)
      - Foreign Commerce Act, 1957, 1959, undated (Box 53, Folder 851-852)
      - Hamilton, Alexander: "Report on Manufactures", undated (Box 53, Folder 853)
      - House Ways and Means Committee, 1957-1959, undated (Box 53, Folder 854)
      - Lead and zinc hearings, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 855)
      - Lloyd statement before Senate Finance Committee, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 856)
      - Majority report: H.R. 12591, 1958, undated (Box 53, Folder 857-858)
      - O.D.M.: Domestic watch and clock hearings, 1956, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 859)
      - O.D.M.: Petroleum hearings, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 860)
      - 0.D.M.: Wool hearings, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 861)
      - O.T.C./G.A.T.T., H.R. 6630, 1956, 1957, undated (Box 54, Folder 862)
      - Presidential messages, 1957, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 863)
      - Reed, Daniel A., 1957, 1958, undated (Box 54, Folder 864-865)
      - Senate Finance Committee, 1957 (Box 54, Folder 866)
      - Simpson bills, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 867-869)
      - Simpson-Davis bill, 1958, n.d (Box 54, Folder 870)
      - Telegrams re H.R. 12591, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 871)
      - Trade Agreements Act: Proposed amendments, 1958, undated (Box 54, Folder 872)
      - Widnall: Reprint of Helfrich statement, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 873)
      - Withrow: Trade Agreements Act, 1958, undated (Box 54, Folder 874)
      - H.R. 10368, 1957, 1958, undated (Box 54, Folder 875-878)
      - H.R. 12591, 1958-1960, undated (Box 54, Folder 879-883)
    - Companies
      - Allied Chemical Corporations, 1957-1962 (Box 55, Folder 884)
      - American Cotton Manufacturers Institute, Inc., 1956-1959 (Box 55, Folder 885)
      - American Cyanimid Company, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 886)
      - The American Thread Company, 1958, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 887)
      - American Tool and Works Company, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 888)
      - American Viscose Corporation, 1957-1962 (Box 55, Folder 889-890)
      - American Zinc, Lead, and Smelting Company, 1958-1962 (Box 55, Folder 891)
      - Chemstrand Corporation, 1958-1959 (Box 55, Folder 892)
      - The Cincinnati Milling Machine Company, 1956-1959 (Box 55, Folder 893)
      - Clock and Watch Manufacturers Association of America Inc., 1957, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 894)
      - Dow Chemical Company, 1956-1957 (Box 55, Folder 895-899)
      - Draper Corporation, 1958-1962 (Box 55, Folder 900)
      - E.I. du Pont de Nemours and Company, 1956-1958 May (Box 55, Folder 901-903)
      - E.I. du Pont de Nemours and Company, 1958 July-1962 (Box 56, Folder 904-905)
      - The B.F. Goodrich Company, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 906)
      - Hardboard Association, 1956-1958, undated (Box 56, Folder 907)
      - Helfrich, Karl, 1956-1958, undated (Box 56, Folder 908-909)
      - Ingraham, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 910)
      - Koppers Company, Inc., 1957-1961 (Box 56, Folder 911)
      - Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Company, 1956-1958 (Box 56, Folder 912-913)
      - John P. Maguire and Company, Inc., 1957-1959 (Box 56, Folder 914)
      - Maloney Electric Company, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 915)
      - Masonite Corporations, 1956-1958 (Box 56, Folder 916)
      - Mississippi Glass Company, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 917)
      - Monsanto Chemical Company, 1956-1958 (Box 56, Folder 918-923)
      - The Okonite Company, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 924)
      - Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1958, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 925)
      - Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company, 1956-1957 (Box 56, Folder 926)
      - Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 927-929)
      - Rockwell Manufacturing Company, 1956 (Box 57, Folder 930)
      - Saco-Lowell Shops, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 931)
      - St. Joseph Lead Company, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 932)
      - Titan Metal Manufacturing Company, 1958, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 933)
      - The Torrington Company, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 934)
      - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1956-1959 (Box 57, Folder 935)
    - Publications
      - The American Woman and Foreign Trade, 1957, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 936)
      - Campaign manual, 1957, undated (Box 57, Folder 937-938)
      - Facts and Fallacies, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 939)
      - The Farmer and the Octopus, 1956-1958, undated (Box 57, Folder 940-941)
      - Fund Raising Booklet, undated (Box 57, Folder 942)
      - G.A.T.T Spells TROUBLE, 1957, undated (Box 57, Folder 943)
      - Is your job for export?, undated (Box 57, Folder 944)
      - Speaker's manual, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 945)
      - Tariffs are a job's best friend, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 946)
      - Thoughtful Businessman, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 947)
      - It's Time to Stop Exporting American Jobs, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 948)
      - Trade Surveys, Analysis of, undated (Box 57, Folder 949)
  - Trade Relations Council
    - General Correspondence, 1959-1962, undated (Box 58, Folder 950-959)
    - Select correspondence
      - Nowling, Jack R., 1959, 1960, undated (Box 58, Folder 960)
      - Correspondence with newspapers, 1962, undated (Box 58, Folder 961)
    - Topical files
      - Action program, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 962)
      - Advertisement, 1960, undated (Box 59, Folder 963)
      - Advertising Club speech, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 964)
      - A.F.L.-C.I.O., 1960 (Box 59, Folder 965)
      - Announcement of new president, 1956-1960, undated (Box 59, Folder 966)
      - Announcement of Trade Relations Council, 1959, undated (Box 59, Folder 967)
      - Annual meetings, 1959-1961 (Box 59, Folder 968-970)
      - Anthony, Richard H., 1961-1963, undated (Box 59, Folder 971-973)
      - Antidumping, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 974)
      - Ashley, James M., 1962, 1963, undated (Box 59, Folder 975)
      - Background material, 1958, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 976-978)
      - Balance of payments, 1958-1962, undated (Box 60, Folder 979-986)
      - Bills: Foreign trade, 1958, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 987)
      - Bills: House of Representatives, 1958, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 988)
      - Bills: Senate, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 989)
      - Board of Trustees, 1959-1962, undated (Box 60, Folder 990-991)
      - Byrd letter, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 992)
      - Chamber of Commerce of the U.S., 1959-1962, undated (Box 61, Folder 993-996)
      - Citizen Action Workshops, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 997)
      - Committee for Reciprocity Information, 1960, 1961, undated (Box 61, Folder 998)
      - Congressional Candidate Contact Campaign, 1958-1960 (Box 61, Folder 999-1003)
      - Congressional reports, 1962, undated (Box 61, Folder 1004-1006)
      - Congressional reprints, 1958-1961 (Box 62, Folder 1007)
      - Congressional speeches, 1959, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1008)
      - Conventions: National Republican and Democratic, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1009-1011)
      - Copper and Brass Research Association, 1961, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 1012-1013)
      - "Escape clause", 1961, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 1014)
      - Foreign trade, 1959, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 1015-1016)
      - G.A.T.T., 1959, 1960, undated (Box 62, Folder 1017-1022)
      - Hawes, Robert N., 1962, undated (Box 63, Folder 1023-1024)
      - House Ways and Means Committee, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 1025)
      - Inter-Industry Committee program, 1961, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1026)
      - Internal Revenue Service, 1960, 1961, undated (Box 63, Folder 1027)
      - Keeting bill, 1959, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 1028)
      - Legislative proposals, 1960, 1961, undated (Box 63, Folder 1029-1031)
      - Lloyd, Dr. Lewis E., 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1032)
      - Luncheon meeting: Sheraton Carlton Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1959 (Box 63, Folder 1033)
      - Martin, Thomas A., 1959-1962 (Box 63, Folder 1034)
      - National Electrical Manufacturers Association: National Security Committee, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 1035)
      - National Electrical Manufacturers Association: National Security Committee, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 1037)
      - Program objectives, 1960, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 1038)
      - Radio scripts, undated (Box 64, Folder 1039)
      - Sample resolution, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 1040)